Now we publish this result in the journal Nature.
现在我们把这个结果发表在《自然》杂志上
In fact, it became a cover of Nature.
实际上这是《自然》杂志的封面
At the time, it was the fourth most discussed nature paper ever.
当时这是第四大热门自然类论文
And it really raised a lot of questions.
引发了许多问题
What is the future of medicine look like if effectively,
如果的确有效 照相机系统可以比最好的人类医生更加出色
a camera-based system can outperform the best human doctors?
医学的未来是什么？
Now what I want to caution here a little
现在我要提醒一下
bit because this is a study done on images alone.
因为这个研究只是根据图像进行的
And a doctor does much more than just looking at images.
而医生不仅仅依靠观察图像
He knows the patient.
他了解病人
There would be an impression of the patient and so on.
可能是对病人的印象等等
But still, a shocking an image-based said that effectively,
不过如果以图像为基础的系统有效
an iPhone does as well as a highly paid doctor.
那么 iPhone 能够和收入很高的医生做得一样好
And that discussion is ongoing.
相关讨论仍在持续
The reason why I want you to do this on your own now in an exercise and
希望你独立完成这个练习
experience the same phenomena with this more data set is because,
体验更多数据集的相同现象
what you're learning here in this class,
原因在于你在深度学习这节课学到的内容
in Deep Learning has the potential to massively change how the society works.
有可能会对社会运转做出巨大改变
Many of us, many of us do the same repetitive task every day, in and out.
我们许多人每天都做着重复性工作 日复一日
We might be lawyers doing contract drafting or a legal document discovery.
我们可能是律师 草拟合同或法律文本
You might be doctors trying to catch cancer.
可能是医生 希望治愈癌症
You might be truck drivers driving trucks.
可能是开卡车的司机
Pilots flying planes.
开飞机的飞行员
Researchers doing financial investment research on the web.
研究金融投资的研究人员
Brokers, insurance brokers.
经纪人 保险经纪人
All of us do the same thing over and over again.
我们都在不断重复相同的事情
And what AI can do with us,
人工智能能够带来的改变是
it can make us super human.
它可以让我们成为超人类
Given the capability of the best of demontologist and give it to everybody.
考虑到最佳皮肤科医生的能力 把这个能力赋予每个人
The capabilities of the best accountants and give it to everybody.
考虑到最佳会计的能力 把这个能力赋予每个人
The capabilities of the best salespeople and give it to everybody.
考虑到最佳销售的能力 把这个能力赋予每个人
That's going to be the pure illusion.
这会成为纯粹的设想
And by you taking this course and learning how to apply deeply and interesting problems.
通过学习这节课 学会如何应用到有趣的深层问题
You can make people superhuman and you can probably build a business almost everywhere,
你可以让其他人成为超人类 可以在
where people do highly repetitive office work.
人们进行高度重复性的办公室工作中 创造商业奇迹
I believe Deep Learning will make people five, ten,
我相信深度学习可以让人们的效率提高 5 10 甚至 20 倍
20 times as efficient and as you become more efficient,
当你更有效率时
our jobs will change.
我们的工作会发生改变
A long time ago,
很久以前
a U.S. farmer was able to feed about four people.
一个美国农民可以养活 4 个人
Today, one farmer can feed 155 people in the world.
现在一个美国农民可以养活 155 个人
Today, an account might have 10 clients and 20 clients.
今天一位会计可能有 10 到 20 个客户
In the future might be 150 clients, a thousand clients.
未来一位会计可能有 150 个甚至 1000 个客户
If you think about this,
如果你能考虑到这些
the potential of these technology is unbelievable.
你会发现 AI 技术的潜力是难以置信的